meditationbangles.com 2015-03-03

# Frequency Bangles

MeditationBangles.com (Nick Hodgson, Owner) respects and is committed to protecting your personal privacy. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and is only used to process orders and to provide a more personalized shopping experience.It is our strict policy not to sell, rent, share or loan any identifiable information (including our mailing list) to anyone.Please read on for more details about our privacy policy. 

What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Use It?  
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit-card number and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your orders and to notify you of your order status.

You may voluntarily sign up to be informed about certain offers. For this service we need only an e-mail address, which we use to send the information you requested. 

When you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and e-mail address, so we can administer the contest and notify winners. 

We personalize your shopping experience by using your purchases to shape our recommendations about other merchandise that might be of interest to you. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop the design and layout of the store. 

We may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you about important changes to the Web site, new MeditationBangles.com services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive this information, please notify us. Make sure to notify us for each account or e-mail address you have left with us. 

How Does MeditationBangles.com Protect Customer Information?  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Specifically, our customer database is password protected and contains no credit card numbers, and all transactions are conducted over a SSL (Secure Socket Layer, as ensured by InstantSSL) connection and processed on a secure server. To view and edit your customer information please log in using your MeditationBangles.com username and password and navigate to the account info page.

What About "Cookies"?   
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information or credit card numbers, but they do enable us to provide features such as 1-Click shopping and to store items in your shopping cart between visits. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them. 

Will MeditationBangles.com Disclose the Information it Collects to Outside Parties?   
MeditationBangles.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending a blank e-mail message to info@MeditationBangles.com.com. (If you use more than one e-mail address to shop with us, send this message from each e-mail account you use.) Also, MeditationBangles.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information. 

In Summary   
We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at MeditationBangles.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may choose to do so in the future with trustworthy third parties, but you can tell us not to by sending us an e-mail message.

Your Consent   
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by MeditationBangles.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

Tell Us What You Think  
MeditationBangles.com welcomes your questions and comments about privacy. Please e-mail us at [info@MeditationBangles.com.com](mailto:askastrogems@gmail.com).
